Take it outside.
Road House is a action, thriller film directed by Doug Liman.
Ex-UFC fighter Dalton takes a job as a bouncer at a Florida Keys roadhouse,
only to discover that this paradise is not all it seems.
Dalton, played by Jake Gyllenhaal.
Ben Brandt, played by Billy Magnussen.
Dex, played by Travis Van Winkle.
Sam, played by Darren Barnet.
Ellie, played by Daniela Melchior.
Frankie, played by Jessica Williams.
Road House is a 2024 American action film, which is a remake of Road
House and the third movie overall in the same franchise.
Directed by Doug Liman from a script written by Anthony Bagarozzi and Chuck Mondry, some of the
characters and events of the story are similar to those of the original release.
It stars Jake Gyllenhaal as an ex-UFC fighter who takes a job
as a bouncer at a Florida Keys road house.
Produced by Joel Silver, the movie also features Daniela Melchior, Billy Magnussen, Jessica Williams,
Joaquim de Almeida, JD Pardo, Austin Post, and Conor McGregor in its supporting cast.
Road House premiered on March 8, 2024, at the opening night of the South by Southwest
festival, and was released by Amazon MGM Studios via Prime Video on March 21, 2024.
It received mixed reviews from critics.
A sequel is in development.
The film explores themes of florida keys, mixed martial
arts (mma), remake, bouncer, fighting.
The tone is intense.